question_data = [
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Stevie Wonder&#039;s real name is Stevland Hardaway Morris.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "The music group Daft Punk got their name from a negative review they recieved.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "In 1993, Prince changed his name to an unpronounceable symbol because he was unhappy with his contract with Warner Bros.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "American rapper Dr. Dre actually has a Ph.D. doctorate.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Muse is a British (English) rock band",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Daft Punk originated in France.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "The alternative rock band, They Might Be Giants, released their album &#039;Flood&#039; in 1990. ",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "John Williams composed the music for &quot;Star Wars&quot;.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Eurobeat is primarily an Italian genre of music.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "The song &quot;Stronger Than You&quot; is a single by Estelle, who played Garnet in Steven Universe.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        }
    ]